последец
Continue
ئjek
H alter
For crema
Frois
Tears
I really want to stab myself, but
But at that time, my personality would change.
Our personalities are so different from each other
Hello, this is Miku Ishinose.
Today, I was invited to participate in a project.
I've been invited to a project where I'm supposed to go on a date with two men.
And the project is to decide which date was better.
I'm very nervous.
I'm nervous, but I'll get right to it.
I'm going to meet the first one.
I'm going to go see the first one.
The prince of treasures and
In terms of anime characters...
Hi-Q's
Stacy.
There's a character called "Stacie" in HIQ.
I like the serious one a lot.
But as a person, my fans are more interested in him.
They tend to tell me how much they like me and how cute I am.
I like that kind of person.
I like people like that.
From the front?
I'm pretty indecisive.
I'm not good at deciding what I want to do.
Yes.
I'd be very happy if you take me to a place you think I'd like to go.
So I'm waiting for a date.
I'm a little nervous.
I'll take that as a sign...
Good morning.
Are you waiting for me?
No, I'm not!
You're so cute.
Good morning!
May I take a closer look at your clothes?
You're so cute! What? You're shutting off!
Is it cool?
I picked it out for Miku.
So today, I'm going to spend the day on a date of my own devising.
I'm going to entertain Miku.
Shall we go?
We're at the entrance.
It's dark.
What is this place?
This is Team Lab.
TeamLab?
Yes, sir.
I was allowed to plan the date.
I've been thinking about it.
Yes, sir.
It's so dark. Have you been here before, Hinata?
I came once for date stamina.
You did?
Looks like she's popular.
Sounds great.
It's a little off, just a little from here.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
It's a pool!
There's towels.
Ready, go!
What's this?
Oh, my God...
He's so cute.
You're dancing the whole time?
That's amazing.
Look at the sparkles.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
Oh, my God.
Super cute.
It's too cute.
Oh, my God.
That's just too cute.
That's too cute!
He's so cute!
Look, he's bringing the camera!
I'm so happy!
I'll try to capture lots of cute Miku with my camera!
Wow, she's so beautiful!
Oh, I've lost it!
It's so hard!
I messed up!
Oh, it's so cute!
Oh, I'm so cute!
Oh, I'm so confused
Oh, I'm so confused!
sea
Umi.
What are your hobbies?
My hobbies?
I only play video games and watch anime.
Oh, really?
I've always played video games and watched anime.
So you're pretty much an indoor person?
Indoors.
That's why.
Dating...
Mm-hmm.
It's an entrance.
Why, why, why, what happened? Wait a minute.
What? Did it come in this way?
Yeah, it came in this way.
That's fucked up!
I'm a jerk!
I was about to go to the next place, but this is the entrance.
You're pretty clumsy, aren't you?
I was about to go to the next place, but here's the entrance...
I'm really looking forward to the next one.
I want to take lots of pictures.
What? What? What's this?
What's this? What's this?
Look at this.
What's this? What is this? Oh, my God.
What? Oh, my God.
That's too cute.
Oh, my God.
You'd be surprised.
What do you think of today's beauties?
You definitely can't go on a date with her today.
Because I did something that I shouldn't have done.
What did you do?
I overslept.
I wore no makeup.
I really did.
That's amazing.
I didn't know I could move so fast.
I can move so fast.
Amazing.
Harushiro wearing an accessory he doesn't like
Hinata-kun loves everything
Unbelievably cute
He's so cute
Too cute.
I really don't have anything to say about it, it's about 120 points.
I was so surprised at how much we made together!
They even held our hands when we were getting wet all the time.
They gave us slippers and towels for both of us.
He was so kind and complimented me a lot afterwards.
I think Hinata-kun is the only guy who's ever told me how cute I am on a date.
I think he's the only one who's ever told me how cute I was on a date.
He was so cute, I felt like I should've counted it.
So...
Suzu, where are we?
The arcade.
You love it, don't you, Suzu?
So next time, I'd like to enjoy an arcade date.
I'm off.
Glad you're here.
I'm going to take a picture
Excited!
Actually, I love arcade games and I'm a good UFO catcher.
Oh, really?
I always play the cute ones that I like.
I'm a sucker for candy.
Do you like Lovie's?
I do.
I miss you.
You like it? Don't you like it?
I made you a dream.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
He's so cute.
And this one.
It's good, right?
Take a picture.
He's sitting like that.
I don't see any Canucks.
I'm going to miss you. I'm going to miss you.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'll take your picture.
Oh, it looks good on you.
Are you sure?
It's cool.
It's a little darker.
It's good.
Oh, my God.
Is that how you stop it?
Let's go next time.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
I can't see again.
I want this.
Let's do it.
Would you rather I cry?
I don't care either way.
I want a marshmallow. I want a marshmallow.
That's cute.
I'm serious.
I don't care either way.
This one, too.
You can have it.
You can have it, you can have it, you can have it.
I'm sure we can get one of these.
I'm gonna get one of these for sure.
Like a long kiss?
I'm sure we can get a long kiss, right?
We'll get rich quick on this one, too.
Let's take a bunch of pictures and go home.
Got it.
That's great!
I got one!
That's what I'm talking about.
Wait a minute.
Because...
It's Miku's present!
I'm so happy!
Okay, Miku, let's wear these together.
Oh, I like it.
Bracelet!
I need two more.
I'll take care of it.
I got it.
Wait a minute.
I need two more.
Bullshit. Two.
You want this one?
Oh, no, one.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna need two more.
Oh, good.
I'm so glad.
We're together.
Pose as a couple.
Go ahead, let's do it.
Cute.
It says you had fun.
Ta-da!
Done.
He gave it to me.
Ta-da!
My date with Hinata is over.
Next is the second one.
I heard a boy is coming.
Who will it be?
Is he here yet?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello. - Hello.
What's your name?
Naoki.
May I ask you a fashion point?
I prepared it myself today.
Oh, really?
What's wrong?
Yes, I worked hard to prepare it.
It looks great.
Really?
It looks great on you.
You look cute.
But since this morning...
You must have gotten a lot of scratches from chicks.
Yeah, I have.
That's why.
I'll give you a little more.
I'm so embarrassed.
Let's go.
Let's go!
It's okay.
I don't know.
You've been here before, right?
That's right.
That was a lot of fun.
I thought maybe the two of us could come here today.
I see.
That's why I chose it.
I'm glad.
It's fun.
Are you having fun?
Yeah.
But I really want to win today.
I really do.
It's so unfair.
The cuteness.
I think it's reddish.
It's embarrassing.
It's cute.
I want to be cute
I miss seeing it
I miss it
Nostalgic! Nostalgic toys!
I want to play.
What's this?
It's bowling.
You want to go?
I'm sorry. Thank you.
I'm in.
I'll buy three.
You're heavier than I thought you'd be.
Go for it, go for it.
Oh, my God.
I did it with both hands.
Oh, wait, I haven't seen anything cool yet.
I'm starting now.
I'm gonna take them all down.
He's cute.
That didn't work.
You should aim for the middle one right here in front of you.
Hey, that's usually what I say.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
Stop it, please.
Don't do that.
You're better than me. Stop it.
You're really good at bowling.
Really?
Hey, I'm...
Why are you doing this to me?
What are you doing to me?
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
You don't need to bowl so bad.
It's okay, I can't do it.
You're so good at bowling. Stop it, please.
As long as it's fun, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, my God, it's a haunted house.
Well...
I'm scared.
It looks scary.
I'd love to be Scott.
What about the ghost? I'm good with ghosts.
Let's get a little closer.
You want to get a little closer?
You don't know what to do?
What? I'm scared.
I'd like to escort you, but...
But I'm scared.
Let's go in.
Are you sure?
Let's just hang on a second.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's go for it.
Sit down, it's really bad.
I'm scared.
Yeah.
There was a girl called Micchan
She's a cute girl
She was popular with the boys
Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Look at this.
Wait a minute.
Is there anyone in here?
What's this?
I'm gonna run.
Ready?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I really can't.
No, no, no, no, no!
Where do you want me to go?
This way?
Don't go, Mikkun.
Come here.
Wait a minute, Mikkun, don't go.
I'll get out of here!
Stop! Stop!
Stop it!
Wait a minute! Mikkun, you're in trouble!
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
It just keeps going and going.
I'm just...
I'm tired.
Oh, shit.
That was really scary.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That was scary.
I think I almost didn't get anything on the camera.
I don't know. It's like...
I mean, I'm cute and all, but...
I'm cute, but I want to be cool.
I think women are more like that.
And that also overrides the female instinct.
I think it's cute that she's a little naive in spite of herself.
That was fun.
Do you want to take a break?
Didn't we come here before?
I think I've been here before.
Which one of these foods?
It's kind of useless.
What's wrong?
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
They asked me to do it.
Oh, wild, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no.
Looks so good!
Bon appétit!
It smells so good!
Hot?
It's good.
Hot.
Is it good?
It's good!
I've never tasted tea like this before.
It's lovely.
Come here.
It's hot.
That's cute.
I want to feed it to you.
You're gonna feed it to me?
But it's hot.
I don't think I can take more than one bite.
I don't know. It's kind of giving me that maternal giggle.
Well, you know what?
I've never been on a date before.
I don't know what it's like.
I'm in trouble.
You're in trouble.
He's cute.
Is it hot?
It's out there, but can you see it?
I see it.
The ocean.
I wanted to come to the sea.
Last time I was here, it was in the evening.
Oh, look out!
I came to the beach in the evening.
It's so bright today.
Yes, the beach in the daytime.
Pretty girl.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
GO!
What? Oh, no.
Lukewarm.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no.
It's warm.
It feels so good, this temperature.
There you go.
Oh, no.
Aw, jeez.
Ha-ha-ha.
Cute.
It's fun.
She's so hot.
You should date me again.
Let's do it.
When?
When? - When it's big.
Did you see it pop? I saw it in the shadow.
Yeah, it's okay.
Wow. There you go.
Fast forward.
First of all, Hinata-kun.
He's a handsome guy.
He took a lot of pictures for me.
He took a lot of pictures, and he wanted to leave us with a lot of memories.
I was so happy that he made this day a memorable one.
I had a lot of fun the whole time.
Thank you so much!
Naoki!
Naoki is a cool guy.
but his pampered nature on the beach
It tickles my motherly instinct.
And when I thought about it, he suddenly looked really handsome.
It made my heart swell.
Thank you very much for your thoughtful consideration.
This is...
I had a lot of fun with Miku for a day and a night, and it made me want to go to more places in the future.
I wanted to go to many places in the future.
The way you look at me every moment is so cute.
I want her to be mine!
I love you so much!
Thank you so much, I love you.
My parents are really clumsy.
I tried to be cool like a man, but I just couldn't do it.
I've probably been a little bit uncool in a lot of ways.
I'm so proud of you!
I love your smile more than anything in the world.
Thank you.
I love you so much.
I love you so much!
Please, please.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You're both so cool.
I don't have anything negative to say about them.
No, I didn't get the UFO catcher at all.
I was scared the whole time, too. The haunted house.
I mean, we both had a little bit of, you know, donkusai and stuff.
But I was so excited that I couldn't make up my mind.
So I'm going to ask you to shout a few words into the ocean.
The one with the loudest voice will be the first one to speak today.
You're kidding me.
Okay, let's start with you, Hinata.
Miku! I love you!
(laughs)
You're so precious to me.
LOL!
What will I do if I can't say anything after this?
Does that mean I love you more than you love me?
That's not what I meant.
It's fine.
I don't know what I did to deserve this.
She's staring at me.
I'm sure they're staring at me, too.
Miku!
I've always loved you!
Thank you.
Which one, which one, which one?
You're a good player.
It's been a long time for me too!
I got it.
I love you, man.
Don't forget about me.
Of course you were cool.
I love you.
He's so cute.
Oh, shit.
So...
With Hinata-kun and Naoki-kun
We had a wonderful summer memory date.
I'm so glad I could do it!
I hope you all had a good time.
Did you have a good time?
Did you?
So please subscribe to our channel
Please give us a high rating!
See you soon!
I'm sure we'll do a second one.
I'll definitely do a second one.
I'll definitely win.
No, you won't.